Where the future is your past.
Vice is a thriller, science fiction, action film directed by Brian A. Miller.
Julian Michaels has designed the ultimate resort: VICE, where anything goes and the customers can play out
their wildest fantasies with artificial inhabitants who look, think and feel like humans.
When an artificial becomes self-aware and escapes, she finds herself caught in the crossfire between Julian's
mercenaries and a cop who is hell-bent on shutting down Vice, and stopping the violence once and for all.
Kelly, played by Ambyr Childers.
Roy, played by Thomas Jane.
Evan, played by Bryan Greenberg.
Julian, played by Bruce Willis.
Chris, played by Johnathon Schaech.
Melissa, played by Charlotte Kirk.
Vice is a 2015 American science fiction action film directed by Brian A.
Miller and written by Andre Fabrizio and Jeremy Passmore.
The film stars Thomas Jane, Bruce Willis, and Ambyr Childers.
The plot follows Julian Michaels (Willis), who has opened a resort with questionable ethics,
where people can act out their fiercest fantasies with the resort's androids.
When one of the androids, Kelly (Childers), becomes sentient and escapes, she joins forces with
police detective Roy Tedeschi (Jane) to bring Michaels down and destroy his resort.
The film was panned by critics and is considered
Bruce Willis' worst film to date.
The film explores themes of android, artificial
intelligence (a.i.), virtual reality, mercenary, cop.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.